https://www.riversports.com/terms-of-service/

Skip to primary navigation Skip to main content Skip to footer4CRS Privacy Policy
We value privacy as much as you do. In short, any personal details collected on any of our customers, both in-store or online, will remain confidential. We will not to share any information we gather with anyone outside our company. All data collected is for internal use only.
We will occasionally use your contact information to send you emails or postcards regarding sales, events, news or product information. If you wish to no longer receive this info, please contact us and let us know you’d like to be removed from our contact list. For more detailed information, please read our full Terms of Service listed below
Terms of Service
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which 4Corners Riversports collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://www.riversports.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by 4Corners Riversports.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, fill out a form,respond to a survey, subscribe to the newsletter and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card information.
Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.
We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
Third party platforms may place cookies on your browser for targeted advertising purposes.
How we use collected information
4Corners Riversports collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer service
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To process transactions
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
To send periodic emailsThe email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website\’s own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
4Corners Riversports has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page,. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Questions
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature. When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes. Like many websites, we use “cookies” to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. We may also gather information including your IP Address, Cookie Identifiers, Tracking Pixels to track end-user website behavior. We may also use hashed identifiers derived from email addresses for the purposes of cross-device tracking for targeted advertising. Please refer to the “Do we use ‘cookies’?” section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested. To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests. To quickly process your transactions. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature. If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the “How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?” section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and ‘members-only’ content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.
How do we protect visitor information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.
Do we use “cookies”?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. Third party platforms may also place cookies on your browser for targeted advertising purposes. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won’t have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.
Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term “outside parties” does not include our business. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?
Please see the “Contacting Us” section below or submit a removal request via our online contact form. Please send your full name, email, phone number and address with a note about how your would like to be removed from our customer database. Please take note that once we remove you from our system, we will no longer have access to your sales history for future reference. You can also learn more about opting out of user tracking and targeted advertising here: http://optout.networkadvertising.org/
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
4Corners Riversports
360 S. Camino Del Rio
Durango, CO 81301
970-259-3893
https://www.riversports.com
info@riversports.com
Updated: July 25, 2019Footer
Blog Posts
2020 4CRS Holiday Sale Starts November 9th
Demo SUP, Rec Kayak, Raft & Gear Sale – Sept 23rd
Demo Whitewater Kayak & Inflatable Kayak Sale – Sept 2nd
Business Hours
Fall business hours:
9am to 5pm Mon-Sat
Closed SUN
SHOWROOM NOW OPEN
WEB & PHONE ORDERS SHIPPING DAILY
4Corners Riversports
360 S. Camino del Rio, Ste. 100Durango, CO 81301
970-259-3893
800-426-7637
Newsletter Sign Up
Shop
Kayak / Canoe
Kayaks
Whitewater KayaksInflatable KayaksPack RaftsFishing KayaksTouring & Rec KayaksPedal Drive KayaksKids KayaksUsed Kayaks Back
Kayaking Gear
Kayak PaddlesSpray SkirtsKayak Outfitting & FlotationKayak Fishing AccessoriesHobie AccessoriesRec / Touring Kayak AccessoriesInflatable Kayak AccessoriesKayak Repair & Care Back
Canoes & Acc.
CanoesCanoe PaddlesCanoe AccessoriesCanoe Repair & Care Back
Back
Raft / Cat
Rafts & Catarafts
RaftsCataraftsFishing Rafts & CatsPack RaftsFrames & Frame PartsOars, Paddles & Acc Back
Rafting Gear
Straps / Rigging & AccessoriesDry BoxesCoolersBiminis & ShadeRaft PumpsRaft Repair & Care Back
Back
SUP / Surf
Stand Up Paddle Boards
Inflatable Paddle BoardsRigid Paddle BoardsWhitewater Paddle Boards Back
Paddle Board Gear
Stand Up PaddlesSUP Fins & AccessoriesSUP PumpsPaddle Board Repair & Care Back
Back
Apparel
Mens Apparel
Mens Dry WearMens Splash WearMens Thermal LayeringMens Casual & Swim WearMens FootwearHats & VisorsGloves, Pogies & Skull CapsKids Apparel Back
Womens Apparel
Womens Dry WearWomens Splash WearWomens Thermal LayeringWomens Casual & Swim WearWomens FootwearHats & VisorsGloves, Pogies & Skull CapsKids Apparel Back
Back
Safety
PFDs / Lifejackets
Mens PFDsWomens PFDsYouth PFDsRescue PFDsInflatable PFDsDog PFDs Back
Helmets & Safety
Helmets & AccRiver KnivesThrow BagsRope / Biners / PulleysFirst Aid & Emergency Back
Back
Camp / Kitchen
Group Gear
Camp & KitchenFire Pans & Acc.Water & DishesTables & ChairsToilet SystemsCoolers Back
Personal Gear
Paco & Sleeping PadsDry BagsGear Bags & DuffelsPelican & Dry CasesHeadlamps & Lanterns Back
Back
More
Guides, Books & DVDs
Guide BooksGrand Canyon Books Back
Transport & Storage
Cam & Loop StrapsYakima RacksCargo Boxes & BasketsTransport & Storage Back
River Toys & Games
Speakers & ElectronicsOneWheel XR Electric BoardOneWheel Pint Electric BoardRiver Tubes & Water ToysCamp GamesCoozies & Misc Personal Gear Back
Back
Manufacturers
4CRSAdidasAIREAlpacaAstralBadfishBlack DiamondBlue Sky BoatworksBoardworksCambridge WeldingCanyon CoolersCarlisleCarlsonCarve DesignsCataractChacoCoyoteDaggerDown River EquipmentDownStream River GearEcoXGearFCSFireside OutdoorGFormGear AidGoProGSI OutdoorsGTSHalaHarmonyHobieHurricaneImmersion ResearchInland MarineJack’s Plastic WeldingJackson KayakKatadynKavuKeltyKokatatLiquidLogicLodgeMad RiverMPowerdNRSOnewheelOutdoor ResearchPartner SteelPatagoniaPelican CasesPerceptionPyranhaRAM MountsRivermapsRuffwearSalamanderSawyerScottySeattle SportsShred ReadySnap DragonSOLStohlquistSweet ProtectionTravel ChairWatershedWerner PaddlesWest SystemsWestwater BooksWhitewater DesignsWilderness SystemsWRSIYakAttackYakimaYeti Coolers Back
USED / DEMO
Used Equipment
Used KayaksUsed Paddle BoardsUsed Rafts & GearUsed PaddlesUsed PFDs & Paddling Gear Back
Back
SALE Back
Info
River Info
Local River BetaRiver FlowsRiver PermitsRiver Trip Checklist Back
Product Info
Buying GuidesRepair & CareSize Charts & Fit ListsManufacturers Back
Blog
Product ReviewsTrip ReportsEventsAll Blog Articles Back
Other
Wedding RegistriesPrice Match Policy100% Guarantee15% Off Accessories Back
Back
Services
Rentals
Rentals @ Lake NighthorseRaft RentalsSUP RentalsKayak RentalsCanoe RentalsPaddling Gear RentalsCamp Gear Rentals Back
Paddle School & Instruction
Private InstructionKayak InstructionRaft InstructionSwiftwater RescueACA Instructor Courses Back
Other
Gasket RepairConsignmentGroover CleaningSpring Boat Swap Back
Back
Questions
Contact UsShipping RatesProduct Policies & ReturnsAbout Us Back
